Hey, everybody.
嘿，大家。
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩節快樂。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
What, are we keeping Thanksgiving a secret this year?
什麼，今年我們要保守感恩節的秘密嗎？
No, we are playing this game I learned at work.
不，我們正在玩我在工作中學到的這個遊戲。
You have to name all the states in six minutes.
你必須在六分鐘內說出所有州的名稱。
What?
什麼？
That's, like, insanely easy.
這簡直太簡單了。
No, it's a lot harder than it sounds.
不，這比聽起來困難得多。
You always forget at least one.
你總是會忘記至少一個。
Or, in some cases, fourteen.
或者，在某些情況下，十四個。
It's a stupid game, and it wasn't playing against other people, so,
這是一個愚蠢的遊戲，它不是和其他人玩的，所以，
technically, I didn't lose.
從技術上來說，我並沒有輸。
What, you forgot fourteen states?
什麼，你忘了十四個州？
Nobody cares about the Dakotas.
沒有人關心達科他州。
Oh, okay, time's up.
哦，好吧，時間到了。
All right, I got 48.
好吧，我48了。
Oh, that's not bad.
哦，那還不錯。
Pheebs?
菲比斯？
Oh, I got tired of naming states, so I decided to list the
哦，我厭倦了命名州，所以我決定列出
types of celery.
芹菜的種類。
And I have one, regular celery.
我有一個，普通芹菜。
Okay, so Rachel's got 48, and Phoebe has the lead in...
好的，Rachel 得了 48，Phoebe 領先...
vegetables.
蔬菜。
Joey?
喬伊？
Say hello to the new champ of Chandler's dumb states game.
向錢德勒啞州遊戲的新冠軍問好。
Well, how many you got?
嗯，你有多少？
56.
When it hasn't been your day in weeks, come on, hang out here,
當你已經好幾個星期沒有這樣的日子時，來吧，在這裡閒逛，
but I'll be there for you.
但我會在你身邊。
Hey, how is New England
嘿，新英格蘭怎麼樣
not a state, huh?
不是一個國家，對吧？
They have a sports team.
他們有一支運動隊伍。
Does South Oregon have a sports team?
南俄勒岡有運動隊伍嗎？
There you go.
就這樣吧。
How come we have one extra place setting?
為什麼我們多了一個座位設定？
Because you invited your assistant.
因為你邀請了你的助理。
Oh, right, sorry.
哦，對了，抱歉。
Tarek's not coming.
塔裡克不會來。
His girlfriend came into town, so he's spending Thanksgiving with her.
他的女朋友進城了，所以他要和她一起過感恩節。
Oh, why didn't you tell me?
噢，你為什麼不告訴我？
I made him his own individual sweet potato-stuffed pumpkin.
我為他做了他自己的地瓜南瓜。
Oh, well, I was going to, but then I figured, you know, your
哦，好吧，我本來打算這麼做，但後來我想，你知道，你的
food is so delicious and perfect, you can't ever have too many of
食物是如此美味和完美，你永遠不能吃太多
those pumpkin things.
那些南瓜的東西。
You'd think I wouldn't enjoy that because it is so fake, but I
你可能認為我不會喜歡它，因為它太假了，但我
still do.
仍然如此。
Regular celery!
普通芹菜！
Oh, I already have that.
哦，我已經有了。
Dumb.
啞的。
With time to spare.
有空閒時間。
Ooh, this may be a new world's record.
哦，這可能是一個新的世界紀錄。
You know, I hate to lecture you guys, but it's kind of disgraceful
你知道，我討厭教訓你們，但這有點可恥
that a group of well-educated adults and Joey can't name all the
一群受過良好教育的成年人和喬伊無法說出所有
states.
州。
You ever see a map or one of those round colorful things called
你曾經見過一張地圖或者一種叫做“圓形彩色物體”的東西
a globe?
一個地球儀？
Uh, Magellan?
呃，麥哲倫？
You got 46 states.
你有 46 個州。
What?
什麼？
That's impossible.
那是不可能的。
46.
Well, who's well-educated now, Mr. I-forgot-term-states?
好吧，現在誰受過良好教育，先生，我忘記了術語狀態？
I'm out of oven space.
我的烤箱空間不夠了。
I'm going to go turn on Joey's.
我要去開啟喬伊的電源。
Please watch him.
請注意他。
Do not let Joey eat any of the food.
不要讓喬伊吃任何食物。
I am only one man.
我只是一個人。
Okay, Ross, time is up.
好的，羅斯，時間到了。
No, just give me another minute.
不，再給我一分鐘。
Look, Ross, if you don't know them by now, you will never know
聽著，羅斯，如果你現在還不認識他們，你永遠不會知道
them, okay?
他們，好嗎？
That is the beauty of this game.
這就是這個遊戲的美妙之處。
It makes you want to kill yourself.
它讓你想自殺。
This is crazy.
這太瘋狂了。
I can do this.
我可以做到這一點。
All right, uh, I bet I can get all 50 before dinner.
好吧，呃，我打賭我能在晚餐前拿到全部 50 個。
Okay, but if you can't, no dinner.
好吧，但如果你不能的話，就不吃晚餐了。
You're on.
你開始了。
All right, don't look at my list, Ross, because there's a lot on
好吧，羅斯，別看我的清單，因為上面有很多東西
there that you don't have.
那裡有你沒有的。
Hey, did you guys know that your oven doesn't work?
嘿，你們知道你們的烤箱不工作嗎？
But the drawer full of takeout menus is okay, right?
但抽屜裡裝滿了外帶選單也沒關係，對吧？
Ross, I'm going to use yours, okay?
羅斯，我要用你的，好嗎？
Chandler, give me a hand.
錢德勒，幫我一下。
Sure.
當然。
And Joey, do not let Ross look at any of the maps or
喬伊，不要讓羅斯看任何地圖或
the globe in your apartment.
你公寓裡的地球儀。
Don't worry, Chandler, it's not a globe of the United States.
別擔心，錢德勒，這不是美國的地球儀。
Hey, you guys, I'm going to go out and take a walk.
嘿，你們，我要出去散步。
Phoebe, why is your bag moving?
菲比，你的包包怎麼動了？
Oh, it's not.
哦，不是。
Seriously, it's moving.
說真的，它正在移動。
What the hell's in there?
裡面到底是什麼？
It's just my knitting, that's all.
這只是我的編織，僅此而已。
Yes, I knit this.
是的，這是我織的。
I'm very good.
我很好。
Ross's apartment is nice.
羅斯的公寓不錯。
How come we don't hang out here more often?
為什麼我們不常來這裡玩呢？
I don't know, maybe because it smells a little weird.
我不知道，也許是因為聞起來有點奇怪。
It's like old pumpkins or something.
就像老南瓜什麼的。
That's my pie.
那是我的餡餅。
Which smells delicious.
聞起來很美味。
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
呃-哦，呃-哦。
What?
什麼？
We left Joey alone with the food.
我們留下喬伊一個人拿著食物。
Yep, yep, I knew it.
是的，是的，我就知道。
There he is.
他就在那裡。
Feeding stuffing to a dog.
給狗狗餵食餡料。
Hi, Geller Bing residence.
你好，蓋勒賓住所。
How can I help?
我能提供什麼幫助嗎？
Phoebe, why is there a dog in our apartment?
菲比，為什麼我們的公寓裡有一隻狗？
I'm sorry, who's this?
抱歉，這是誰？
There's a dog sitting on my couch.
我的沙發上坐著一隻狗。
Tell her I'm allergic and I will sue.
告訴她我有過敏，我會告。
No, there's no dog here.
不，這裡沒有狗。
Yes, there is.
是的，有。
He's black and white and shaggy and...
他黑白相間，毛茸茸的，而且…
He's sitting next to Rachel and licking Rachel's hand.
他坐在瑞秋旁邊，舔著瑞秋的手。
Oh my God, where are you?
天哪，你在哪裡？
I'll be right there.
我馬上就到。
They're here already?
他們已經來了？
How are they doing this?
他們是怎麼做的？
Hi, Tag.
嗨，標籤。
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼？
I wanted to see if your offer to spend Thanksgiving with you was
我想看看你提出的和你一起過感恩節的提議是否有效
still good.
還是不錯的。
Sure, come in.
當然，請進來。
What happened to your girlfriend?
你女朋友怎麼了？
We kind of broke up this morning.
今天早上我們就分手了。
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦，對不起。
Yeah, so she went back to Ohio.
是的，所以她回到了俄亥俄州。
Ohio, thank you.
俄亥俄州，謝謝你。
Huh, where's the dog?
呃，狗在哪裡？
What dog?
什麼狗？
There's no dog here.
這裡沒有狗。
Yeah, that dog left.
是的，那隻狗離開了。
Wait a minute, I thought we agreed to say...
等一下，我以為我們同意說...
Your thing, you know?
你的事，你知道嗎？
Phoebe!
菲比！
Phoebe, open up.
菲比，開門。
There's no dog in here.
這裡沒有狗。
Well, uh, hiding the dog plan is off to a great start.
嗯，隱藏狗計劃是一個很好的開始。
Phoebe, we can hear the dog barking.
菲比，我們聽到狗叫了。
No, that's just me coughing.
不，那隻是我咳嗽。
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Oh, good, there you are.
哦，太好了，你來了。
Listen, um, I have a dog in my room.
聽著，嗯，我的房間裡有一隻狗。
What is it doing here?
它在這裡做什麼？
Well, I'm watching it for some friends who went out of town.
嗯，我正在為一些出城的朋友觀看它。
Wait.
等待。
Hello, my name is Clunkers.
大家好，我叫克朗克斯。
May I please stay with you nice people?
我可以和你們這些好人待在一起嗎？
Oh, I wish he would stay here, but Taylor's allergic.
哦，我希望他留在這裡，但泰勒過敏。
Extremely allergic, okay?
非常過敏，好嗎？
If I am anywhere near a dog for more than five minutes, my
如果我靠近狗超過五分鐘，我的
throat will just close up.
喉嚨就會閉合。
That's odd, because this dog's been living here for the past three days.
這很奇怪，因為這隻狗過去三天一直住在這裡。
Really?
真的嗎？
Taylor, if the dog has been here that long and you haven't had
泰勒，如果狗狗已經在這裡那麼久而你還沒有
a reaction, maybe you're not allergic to this dog.
有反應，也許你對這隻狗不過敏。
Well, it still has to go, right?
嗯，還是得走，對吧？
Why?
為什麼？
Okay.
好的。
Okay, it's, um...
好吧，這是，嗯...
Don't do it!
不要這樣做！
Don't do what?
不做什麼？
I have to.
我必須。
Okay?
好的？
It's time.
是時候了。
Okay, I hate dogs.
好吧，我討厭狗。
What?
什麼？
Crazy!
瘋狂的！
Okay.
好的。
They are needy, they are jumpy, and you can't tell what they are
他們很需要幫助，他們很神經質，你無法分辨他們是什麼
thinking, and that scares me a little bit.
思考，這讓我有點害怕。
Right, they are scary.
沒錯，他們很可怕。
Ah!
啊!
She just ate a treat out of my hand!
她剛剛從我手中吃了一頓飯！
So, you're not allergic?
那你不過敏嗎？
I mean, does that mean you're not allergic to wool either?
我的意思是，這是否意味著你也不對羊毛過敏？
You bought me a pink turtleneck sweater.
你買了一件粉紅色高領毛衣給我。
The guy in the catalog pulled it off.
目錄中的那個人成功了。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Do you not like all dogs?
你不喜歡所有的狗嗎？
I mean, not even puppies?
我是說，連小狗都沒有？
Is there a puppy here?
這裡有一隻小狗嗎？
You don't like puppies?
你不喜歡小狗？
Okay, you are new.
好吧，你是新人。
Look, Shannon, I told you, never tell anyone about this dog thing.
聽著，夏農，我告訴過你，永遠不要告訴任何人關於狗的事情。
It's like Ross not liking ice cream.
就像羅斯不喜歡冰淇淋一樣。
You don't like ice cream?
你不喜歡冰淇淋嗎？
It's too cold!
太冷了！
Okay, just the dogs make me a little uncomfortable.
好吧，只是狗讓我有點不舒服。
Where's my key?
我的鑰匙在哪裡？
Now, I don't want to say this, I don't want you guys to
現在，我不想說這個，我不想讓你們說
hate me, but I don't think I can be around that dog anymore.
恨我，但我想我不能再跟那隻狗在一起了。
Okay?
好的？
So, either the dog goes, or I go.
所以，要嘛狗走，要嘛我走。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
How can I not get this?
我怎麼得不到這個呢？
I'm a college professor.
我是大學教授。
I got $14.50 on my SATs.
我的 SAT 成績為 14.50 美元。
$12.50. Damn, I forgot you were here.
12.50 美元。該死，我忘了你在這裡。
All right, we're going to take clunkers to Ross's.
好吧，我們要把舊車帶到羅斯家去。
We'll be back in a minute.
我們一會兒就會回來。
Oh, wait, before you guys go, can I just ask you a question?
哦，等等，在你們離開之前，我可以問你們一個問題嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Um, when a guy breaks up with his girlfriend, what is an appropriate
嗯，當一個男人和他的女朋友分手時，什麼是合適的
amount of time to wait before you make a move?
採取行動之前需要等待多久？
Oh, I'd say about a month.
哦，我想說一個月左右。
Really?
真的嗎？
Let's say three to four.
就說三到四個吧。
Half hour.
半小時。
Interesting.
有趣的。
When it's your assistant, I would say never.
如果是你的助理，我會說永遠不會。
All right, Rach, the big question is, does he like you?
好吧，瑞秋，最大的問題是，他喜歡你嗎？
Right?
正確的？
Because if he doesn't like you, this is all a moo point.
因為如果他不喜歡你，這就是一個問題。
Huh.
呵呵。
A moo point?
哞點？
Yeah.
是的。
It's like a cow's opinion.
這就像牛的意見一樣。
You know?
你知道？
It just doesn't matter.
沒關係。
It's moo.
是哞。
Have I been living with him for too long or did that all
是我和他一起生活太久了還是都這麼做了
just make sense?
有道理嗎？
Please don't listen to Joey.
請不要聽喬伊的話。
Okay?
好的？
Look at him.
看看他。
He's obviously depressed.
他顯然很沮喪。
He's away from his family.
他遠離了家人。
He's spending Thanksgiving with strangers.
他正在和陌生人一起過感恩節。
What he needs right now is for you to be his friend.
他現在需要的是你成為他的朋友。
Oh, you're right.
哦，你是對的。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Okay, that's what I'm going to do.
好吧，這就是我要做的。
Fine.
美好的。
Take their advice.
聽取他們的建議。
No one ever listens to me.
從來沒有人聽我說話。
When the package is this pretty, no one cares what's inside.
當包裝如此漂亮時，沒人會在乎裡面裝的是什麼。
Okay, I'm keeping my end of the deal.
好吧，我遵守協議。
Why is the dog still here?
狗怎麼還在這裡？
We're leaving.
我們要走了。
Okay.
好的。
Bye-bye.
再見。
I can pull this off, right?
我可以完成這個任務，對嗎？
How are you holding up?
你還好嗎？
Not bad.
不錯。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm sorry about your girlfriend, but...
我對你女朋友的事感到抱歉，但是...
So are you guys together a long time?
那你們在一起很久了嗎？
A year, on and off.
一年，斷斷續續。
I kind of thought we'd end up together.
我以為我們最終會在一起。
I don't anymore.
我不再這樣了
Now that she broke up with you?
現在她跟你分手了？
Yeah.
是的。
It's weird.
很奇怪。
I always used to assume that I would meet someone and fall in
我總是以為我會遇到一個人並陷入其中
love and be happy and that all that was just a given.
愛並快樂，而這一切都是既定的。
But lately it's like, what if it's not?
但最近好像，如果不是呢？
Do you ever have that feeling?
你有過這樣的感覺嗎？
No.
不。
Yeah.
是的。
All the time.
一直以來。
Constantly.
不斷地。
It's terrifying.
太可怕了。
But you know, then I figure it has to work out.
但你知道，然後我認為事情一定會成功。
Why?
為什麼？
Because it has to.
因為它必須這樣做。
You really have all the answers, don't you?
你真的已經有了所有的答案，不是嗎？
Yeah, I know, I do.
是的，我知道，我知道。
I really do.
我真的這麼做。
Hey, thanks for talking to me.
嘿，謝謝你跟我說話。
Come on.
快點。
What are bosses for?
老闆是做什麼用的？
Hug it out.
抱抱它出來。
All right, he likes you back.
好吧，他也喜歡你。
See that?
看到了嗎？
Told you you should go for it.
告訴過你應該去爭取。
What?
什麼？
Street noise?
街道噪音？
Drowned any of that out?
淹沒其中的任何一個嗎？
No?
不？
All right, I'll see you later.
好吧，稍後見。
Okay.
好的。
What did Joey say?
喬伊說什麼？
I like you back?
我又喜歡你了？
Yeah, you know, well, see...
是的，你知道，好吧，看...
Joey knows that I'm very insecure about my back.
喬伊知道我對自己的背部非常沒有安全感。
And you were hugging me, so obviously you are not repulsed by it.
而且你還擁抱著我，所以顯然你並不排斥它。
Yeah.
是的。
Wait a minute, that doesn't make any sense.
等一下，這沒有任何意義。
No?
不？
All right.
好的。
Here's the truth.
這是事實。
Joey said what he said, because...
喬伊之所以這麼說，是因為…
I'm attracted to you.
我被你吸引了。
Wow.
哇。
Yeah, I admit it.
是的，我承認。
I have a crush on you, and I know that's crazy, because we
我迷戀你，我知道這很瘋狂，因為我們
work together, and nothing could ever happen.
一起努力，就不會發生什麼事。
And the last thing I want to do is to freak you out
我最不想做的就是嚇到你
or make you feel uncomfortable.
或讓你感到不舒服。
Which is why it would be really great if you said something right
這就是為什麼如果你說得對的話那就太好了
about now.
大約現在。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
Those guys are stealing my car.
那些傢伙正在偷我的車。
What?
什麼？
Right there, that's my car.
就在那裡，那是我的車。
Oh.
哦。
Hey!
嘿！
Okay, well, that's going to take one minute.
好吧，這需要一分鐘。
Do you have anything else you want to get off your chest?
還有什麼想吐露的嗎？
I can't believe this.
我簡直不敢相信這一點。
Wait, we still have time to talk in there.
等等，我們還有時間去那裡談談。
They're not even in the car yet.
他們甚至還沒上車。
Oh, look, there they go.
哦，看，他們走了。
Okay.
好的。
Okay, Phoebe, we should probably go back now.
好吧，菲比，我們現在應該回去了。
Please don't leave me, I'll be lonely.
請不要離開我，我會很孤單。
Stop it.
停止吧。
Stop.
停止。
Okay, let's go.
好吧，我們走吧。
Come on, we can be strong.
加油，我們可以堅強。
Yeah, okay.
是啊，好吧。
Oh my God, did you hear that?
天哪，你聽到了嗎？
She said Monica!
她說莫妮卡！
I can't leave her.
我不能離開她。
You know, if you want, we could sneak the dog back in and
你知道，如果你願意，我們可以把狗偷偷帶回來
Chandler wouldn't even know.
錢德勒甚至不知道。
That's not going to work.
那是行不通的。
I had that dog there for three days and Chandler had no idea.
我把那隻狗放在那裡三天了，錢德勒對此一無所知。
He's not so smart.
他沒那麼聰明。
Hey, I didn't know either.
嘿嘿，我也不知道。
Yeah, but you kind of knew that something was going on, didn't you?
是的，但你知道有些事情正在發生，不是嗎？
Yeah, I knew.
是的，我知道。
Where's Chandler?
錢德勒在哪裡？
Here I am.
我在這裡。
Wash your hands!
洗手！
How did you know?
你怎麼知道的？
Hey, what's she doing back here?
嘿，她回來做什麼？
Relax, Ross, she's not made of ice cream.
放鬆點，羅斯，她不是冰淇淋做的。
Hey, look, Phoebe, I laid out the states geographically.
嘿，看，菲比，我在地理上列出了各州。
No, we don't really have time for this right now, okay?
不，我們現在真的沒有時間，好嗎？
We have to keep Chandler away from my bedroom.
我們必須讓錢德勒遠離我的臥室。
Yeah, but look what I did.
是的，但看看我做了什麼。
See, this is exactly what we do not have time for.
看，這正是我們沒有時間做的事情。
Where's Monica?
莫妮卡在哪裡？
In Phoebe's room.
菲比的房間裡。
You can't go in there.
你不能進去那裡。
Why not?
為什麼不呢？
Monica's crying.
莫妮卡哭了。
She's very upset about this whole clunkers thing.
她對這整件舊車的事情感到非常不安。
Well, I should go in there.
嗯，我應該進去看看。
No, no.
不，不。
No, she doesn't want to see you right now.
不，她現在不想見你。
Why not?
為什麼不呢？
Because you sent away the dog.
因為你把狗送走了。
That's ridiculous.
這太荒謬了。
Oh, is it?
哦，是嗎？
Is it?
是嗎？
Look, when Monica and I were kids, we had a dog named Rover.
聽著，當莫妮卡和我還是個孩子的時候，我們養了一隻名叫羅弗的狗。
And one day, my dad decides he doesn't like dogs.
有一天，我爸爸決定不喜歡狗。
So Monica and her friend, Phyllis, take away the dog.
於是莫妮卡和她的朋友菲利斯把狗帶走了。
And that was the last time we ever saw him.
那是我們最後一次見到他。
Don't you see?
你沒看到嗎？
This is just like that.
就是這樣。
Only with a few details changed.
僅更改了一些細節。
Okay, I'm in my sweatpants.
好吧，我穿著運動褲。
Bring on the food.
把食物端上來。
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
Monica's all upset because I sent clunkers away.
莫妮卡很不高興，因為我把舊車送走了。
So, bring the dog back.
所以，把狗帶回來吧。
You're a hero.
你是一個英雄。
Yeah, I could be a hero.
是的，我可以成為英雄。
I could do that.
我可以做到這一點。
What if it attacks me?
如果它攻擊我怎麼辦？
Yeah, that's like a big gerbil.
是的，就像一隻大沙鼠。
And that doesn't scare you?
這並沒有嚇到你嗎？
Ross, you need some help?
羅斯，你需要幫忙嗎？
From you?
從你那裡？
Yes, please.
是的，請。
First of all, Utah?
首先，猶他州？
Dude, you can't just make stuff up.
夥計，你不能胡編亂造。
Okay, clunkers, come here, you big gerbil.
好吧，老傢伙們，過來，你這個大沙鼠。
Clunkers?
舊車？
Where's my clunkers, my little clunkers?
我的舊車、我的小舊車在哪裡？
No, no, no, I am not going to do that voice.
不，不，不，我不會發出那個聲音。
Clunkers?
舊車？
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Come back here, you furry little butt sniffer.
回來吧，你這個毛茸茸的小屁股嗅探者。
Not you, ma'am.
不是你，女士。
I hate America.
我討厭美國。
When I finish this game, I swear, I am moving.
當我完成這個遊戲時，我發誓，我要搬家了。
Hey.
嘿。
Peg, still talking to the police?
佩格，還在跟警察說話嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Ah, why, damn it, why did I open my mouth?
啊，該死，我為什麼要張開嘴？
I have a crush on you.
我迷戀你。
I am attracted to you.
我被你吸引了。
I mean, I know that I freaked him out.
我是說，我知道我嚇壞了他。
If you said it like that, you probably did, yeah.
如果你這麼說，你可能就這麼做了，是的。
What was I thinking?
我在想什麼？
I work with this man.
我和這個人一起工作。
I have to see him every day.
我每天都必須見到他。
How did this happen to me?
我怎麼會遇到這種事？
Oh, oh wait, that's right, it was because of you.
哦哦等等，沒錯，都是因為你。
All right, all right, I think I can help you.
好吧好吧，我想我可以幫助你。
You want to know what you have to do?
你想知道你必須做什麼嗎？
Please, help me.
請幫我。
Okay, okay, okay.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
Now, all right, you're going to want to talk to him about this,
現在，好吧，你想和他談談這件事，
right?
正確的？
But trust me, Rach, that'll only make it worse.
但相信我，瑞秋，這只會讓事情變得更糟。
You have to deny everything.
你必須否認一切。
That conversation out there, never happened.
那裡的談話從未發生過。
Joey, I don't think that's going to work.
喬伊，我認為這行不通。
It was a pretty long conversation.
這是一次相當長的談話。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, there was no conversation.
嗚嗚嗚，沒有對話。
Joey, I'm just going to talk to Tag.
喬伊，我要和塔格談談。
Who's Tag?
標籤是誰？
There's no Tag.
沒有標籤。
Okay, this conversation is over.
好了，本次對話就結束了。
See, it works.
看，它有效。
Was Chandler here?
錢德勒在嗎？
No, no, he went for a walk.
不，不，他去散步了。
Okay, well you cannot tell him, but look who's back.
好吧，你不能告訴他，但看看誰回來了。
Hi!
你好！
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
He went over to Ross's to bring the dog back here.
他去羅斯家把狗帶回來。
Oh, no, the dog's not going to be there.
哦，不，狗不會在那裡。
You think?
您認為？
Please, please, please, don't be mad at me.
拜託，拜託，拜託，不要生我的氣。
What?
什麼？
Why would she wait and see?
她為什麼要觀望？
Maybe we will, maybe we won't.
也許我們會，也許我們不會。
Okay, I went over to Ross's apartment to bring back clunkers, you know,
好吧，我去羅斯的公寓帶回舊貨，你知道，
for you.
為你。
And I left the door open and she must have gotten out.
我把門開著，她一定已經出去了。
And I looked everywhere, all over the apartment, including the roof.
我到處尋找，整個公寓，包括屋頂。
Which, FYI, Ross, one of your neighbors, growing weed.
僅供參考，羅斯，你的一位鄰居，正在種植雜草。
I couldn't find them.
我找不到他們。
And I am so, so, so sorry.
我非常非常非常抱歉。
But I do know where we can all go ease the pain.
但我確實知道我們可以去哪裡減輕痛苦。
We have good news.
我們有好訊息。
Look who's back!
看看誰回來了！
Hey!
嘿！
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
That's right, she came back all by herself.
沒錯，她是一個人回來的。
It's a Thanksgiving miracle!
這真是感恩節奇蹟！
It is so good to see you.
很高興見到你。
Yes, she came all the way back from Ross's building.
是的，她從羅斯的大樓裡千里迢迢回來了。
Oh, the things she must have seen!
哦，她一定看過這些東西！
And then she climbed up the fire escape, and she tapped on the
然後她爬上消防梯，敲擊
window with her teeny little paw, and then we ran to let her
用她的小爪子開啟窗戶，然後我們跑去讓她
in.
在。
I went too far, didn't I?
我太過分了，不是嗎？
When should I have stopped?
我什麼時候該停止？
Okay, maybe this is so hard because there aren't 50 states.
好吧，也許這很難，因為沒有 50 個州。
Let me tell you something.
讓我告訴你一件事。
I have 49 states.
我有 49 個州。
And there are no more!
沒有更多了！
I think I should be able to eat something.
我想我應該可以吃點東西。
It's up to you.
由你決定。
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨。
How are you doing?
你好嗎？
I'm okay.
我沒事。
I gotta go down to the police station and look at mug shots.
我得去警察局看犯罪嫌疑人照片
Thanks for having me over, you guys.
謝謝你們邀請我過來。
Tag, you're going?
標籤，你要去嗎？
We didn't even get a chance to talk.
我們連說話的機會都沒有。
So where did you say you're from again?
那你說你又從哪裡來？
Colorado.
科羅拉多州。
Ah, what good are you?
啊，你有什麼好？
Look, I think we should talk about what happened on the terrace.
聽著，我想我們應該談談露臺上發生的事情。
Okay.
好的。
I never should have said what I said.
我根本不應該說出我所說的話。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
It just doesn't matter how I feel.
我的感受如何並不重要。
I mean, we work together, so nothing could really ever happen between us.
我的意思是，我們一起工作，所以我們之間不會發生任何事情。
And what I would love is just to go to work on Monday
我所希望的是週一去上班
and never talk about this again.
並且永遠不再談論這件事。
Okay?
好的？
Big day Monday.
週一是個大日子。
Lots to do.
有很多事情要做。
So are we okay?
那我們還好嗎？
Um, I'm not.
嗯，我不是。
Oh, God, I knew it.
哦，上帝，我就知道。
I freaked you out.
我嚇壞你了。
No, you didn't.
不，你沒有。
The only thing that freaked me out was you saying that nothing could
唯一讓我害怕的是你說沒有什麼可以
ever happen between us.
我們之間曾經發生過。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
So please don't fire me for doing this.
所以請不要因為我這樣做而解僱我。
Okay, well, that's one less thing we have to do on Monday.
好吧，這就是我們週一要做的少一件事。
Delaware.
特拉華州。
Hi.
你好。
I want my turkey now.
我現在想要我的火雞。
You got it.
你明白了。
You got Nevada twice.
你兩次獲得內華達州。
I know.
我知道。
Yeah.
是的。